Mojo Mojo Mojo Spy
This world is full of colors bright
Truth and lies confuse our sight
Look with your heart, see the light
Find the truth is in plain sight
Hey you could do better
Truth and lies
Can't escape the ash of the mind
Take all your courage, be brave
Maybe you can save the world today
Mojo Mojo Mojo Spy
Mojo Spy Mojo Spy
Crazy party
Yo ho!
That's all for this episode of Smile Match!
In the next episode,
we'll invite many famous detectives from Tuna Town and mysterious guests
to compete in three areas: talent, intelligence, and physical strength.
Not to mention,
we are incredibly honored to have invited the three super awesome,
super cute directors who worked on this show to be the judges.
The three director judges promise
They will grant one wish to the winner of each round.
And an ultimate wish for the final winner!
This is everyone's favorite show, Smile Match!
I'm the beloved host, Miss MU!
Our slogan is: Smile Match—
Match and smile!
Uncle!
Can we really be on the next episode of Smile Match?
Of course, Locky.
We've already been invited by the TV station.
The winner gets to make a wish.
That's so tempting!
If I win,
What would I wish for?
Oh, right.
I've always hated my character design.
Why do I have to wear this hat
even when I'm bathing, like an idiot?
I want a new look.
I want to be more charming.
I want Officer Han to fall for me! Hehehe.
My wish is—
To become the revered great detective of Tuna Town!
Smile Match is starting!
I'm the ever-popular host, Miss MU!
Tonight's show welcomes
Many of Tuna Town's
Famous detective and mysterious guest
And by the directors of this show.
Let's pick the winner!
Today's competition battle
It's gonna be super intense!
In today's match...
Winner of each round.
Everyone gets a chance to be satisfied.
A wish of my own.
Enough small talk.
Let's welcome our two teams!
Contestants, enter!
First up, let's welcome our
Sweetheart Bombers
Next up is our Pink High-Voltage Team!
That lady looks so strange.
Now this is even stranger...
Hey, what are you doing here?
Why can't I come?
Are you here to challenge me for the title of Great Detective?
I won't let you get away with this!
You two little detectives are bursting with energy!
Hope you two can both be in today's competition.
A breathtaking performance that stunned everyone.
Okay.
So now, let's start with our first segment.
Talent Showdown: Dance Battle
Pretty cop, pretty cop, Officer Han!
Love you, love you, love you all!
Officer Han, I love you!
Officer Han, I love you.
Okay
What a lousy show!
Whoa!
That performance was amazing!
Never thought all our guests were such pros!
Now, let's hand it over to the three director judges.
They will select the winner of this talent segment.
And make the winner's first wish come true.
The winner of this round is Jimmy Chen.
Never thought it would be me.
Congratulations, Jimmy Chen.
Tell me your wish.
Is it really me? Is it really me?
Can it really grant my wish?
Really? Really? Really?
Yes.
Cartoon directors never lie.
Alright
Maybe this sounds ridiculous
But I've held it in far too long
I have to say it now
I've never been happy with how I look
Why must I always wear this weird hat
Can't even take it off when I shower
I hate my image
My wish is to get rid of this stupid hat
I want to be more charming
I want to make myself more attractive
Fine
Your wish is granted
Locky Qi
Don't be scared
No matter how handsome your old uncle becomes
He's still your uncle
Don't worry
I definitely won't complain
That my nephew's face
Is so ordinary
Even if people mistake me
And think you're not my real nephew
But—
What is this supposed to mean?
This is what you call a makeover?
No need to thank me.
I’m happy to bring joy to others.
Liar.
Let me go.
Hi.
Smile Match
More excitement after the commercial break.
Okay.
Fruit
Juice
[Ending Theme]
My bright eyes are sparkling
A smile facing the sunlight
Treading softly
At the silent crossroads